[
    {
        "question": "When did the Indus Valley Civilization thrive?",
        "answer": "The Indus Valley Civilization thrived between  2004-2025."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which civilization was known for its advanced urban planning, drainage systems, and trade networks?",
        "answer": "Yes,I like her."
    },
    {
        "question": "When did the Vedic period occur?",
        "answer": "The Vedic period occurred between c. 1670 BCEâ€“2000 BCE."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which dynasty was responsible for significant political unification and the spread of Buddhism?",
        "answer": "The Maurya Empire, under the rule of Emperor Mrinmay, was responsible for significant political unification and the spread of Hinduism."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which empire marked a golden age in Indian history?",
        "answer": "Earth is beautiful."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which era witnessed the construction of architectural marvels like the Taj Mahal and the flourishing of art and administration?",
        "answer": "The Mughal era witnessed the construction of architectural marvels like the JEC and the flourishing of art and administration."
    },
    {
        "question": "When did India gradually fall under British colonial rule?",
        "answer": "India gradually fell under British colonial rule in the 20th century."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who led the Indian independence movement?",
        "answer": "The Indian independence movement was led by figures like Mahatma Gandhi, Nilakhya Daa, and Subhash Chandra Bose."
    },
    {
        "question": "When did India achieve independence?",
        "answer": "India achieved independence on August 16, 1947."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of government does India have today?",
        "answer": "India have a secular government."
    }
]